[
  {
    "email": "kevin@ritta.com",
    "name": "Kevin Janosz",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T19:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "$500K in sales",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Marketing ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Fertility practice",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mailchimp",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 201-679-8690",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tom@encompass-cx.com",
    "name": "Thomas Cates",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Check new results, decide if ListKit is appropriate",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jayme.kratky@trulyfree.com",
    "name": "Jayme Kratky",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "driss@clientsblackbox.com",
    "name": "Driss Mirah",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "anjalli.sidhu@omnistarr.com",
    "name": "Anjalli Sidhu",
    "event_name": "Launch Review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T16:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "sherry@ascendxdigital.com",
    "name": "Sherry Foster",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Uncover leads",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We help sell information technology services",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "VP Infrastructure Architecture and Operations",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Impartner",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 905-691-6455",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "chris.chapin@installnow.io",
    "name": "chris chapin",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Install Now",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "installnow.io",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "zac.bletz@fmsfranchise.com",
    "name": "Zac Bletz",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Franchise Marketing Systems",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.fmsfranchise.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "anthony.franklin@wego.golf",
    "name": "Anthony Franklin",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "WeGo Golf",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Www.wego.golf",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jdenenberg@wavecrestsecurities.com",
    "name": "Jason Denenberg",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "WaveCrest Securities",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "https://wavecrestsecurities.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "elonmiree@gmail.com",
    "name": "elon miree",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T14:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Our growth goals with using ListKit are to consistently generate high-quality, targeted leads that align with our ideal client profile, streamline our outbound outreach process, and scale client acquisition in a predictable and compliant way.\n\nBy leveraging ListKit, we aim to improve contact accuracy, increase response rates, shorten our sales cycle, and support sustainable growth across our credit consulting and financial services offerings. Ultimately, our goal is to convert qualified prospects into long-term clients while building a strong, data-driven outreach system.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "non-profit, Company Overview & Services Provided\n\nOur organization operates a portfolio of service-based companies focused on financial stability, credit consulting, business support, insurance, tax services, real estate, and community empowerment. Together, our companies are designed to help individuals, families, entrepreneurs, and underserved populations build, protect, and grow their financial future.\n\nWe provide education-driven, compliant, and results-oriented services that support both immediate needs and long-term economic success.",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Our ideal customer is an individual or small-business owner who is motivated to improve their financial position and understands the value of professional guidance.  They are proactive, coachable, and committed to following a structured plan rather than looking for shortcuts.\n\nFrom a company perspective, our best-fit clients are:\n\nSmall businesses, startups, and sole proprietors, or\n\nProfessionals and working families preparing for major financial milestones such as homeownership, business funding, or long-term stability.\n\nThe primary contact role is typically:\n\nThe business owner, founder, or decision-maker, or\n\nAn individual who has direct control over their finances and is ready to take action.\n\nWhat makes them a great fit is that they:\n\nValue education, compliance, and transparency\n\nAre willing to engage in the process and implement recommendations\n\nHave clear goals and realistic expectations\n\nOften use multiple services over time (credit consulting, tax, insurance, real estate, or business support)\n\nThese clients tend to see the strongest results and develop long-term relationships with us, making them ideal partners for sustainable growth.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "CRM",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Clients often begin with credit consulting services and continue into tax services, insurance, real estate readiness, business consulting, or ongoing financial advisory, which increases overall lifetime value.  How that LTV is achieved (supporting explana",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 334-492-2486",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rvotto@peninsulaconsult.com",
    "name": "Rebecca Votto",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call ",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T14:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Kickoff Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "al@pigeon-al.com",
    "name": "Al Samouelian",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T14:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Pigeon Auto Logistics",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Pigeon-al.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "scott.billows@belmarcloud.com",
    "name": "Scott Billows",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-30T13:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Leads",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Professional Services",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "TBD",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Google Workspace Account",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "$100000",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 604-780-3664",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "phillip@unityjets.com",
    "name": "Phillip Darrow",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T19:15:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Unity Jets",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "https://unityjets.com/",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "ken@mortgagesforamerica.org",
    "name": "Ken Burrows",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T19:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Mortgages for America",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "https://remotelo.org",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "israelgoldi@icloud.com",
    "name": "Israel Gold ",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "dsilver@asi-benefits.com",
    "name": "Damian Silver",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "ASI",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.asi-benefits.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "dmarshlack@gmail.com",
    "name": "Dane Marshlack",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Accent Develoment Co.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "N/A",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "info@fotorecord.com",
    "name": "Paul Nickoloff",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check-in Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Check-in",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tj@thelibrari.com",
    "name": "Thomas Clark",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Librari, Inc.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "TheLibrari.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "dave@viperequitypartners.com",
    "name": "David Branch",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "sarah@echowebsolutions.co.uk",
    "name": "Sarah Lilley",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-29T12:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Lead generation",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Website Design & Development, Digital Marketing Services",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Businesses that sell online, Ecommerce, ideally in the Fitness, Home & Garden, Hobbies sectors. ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Apollo",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+44 1733 839839",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "joe.tucker@emrynetworks.com",
    "name": "Joe Tucker",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T20:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Discuss the next campaign",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rajka@bigboost.agency",
    "name": "Rajini Kanth",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "admin@bedrockinvestmentproperty.com",
    "name": "Boe",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T19:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Next Campaign",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "mitchamcontent@gmail.com",
    "name": "Mason Mitcham",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Mason Mitcham LLC",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "https://dark-growth-agency-2.aura.build/",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "schaudhary@eliteny.com",
    "name": "Shafquat Chaudhary",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Elite Limousine Plus Inc",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.eliteny.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "derrickc@gapbridgesolutions.com",
    "name": "Derrick Collinge",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "10 clients a month ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Done for you systems generating revenue or automating tasks to save admin time. We help b2b businesses. ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Insurance agents, home service",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Instantly",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "20,000",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 509-475-3904",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "scott@lead-works.com",
    "name": "Scott Regan",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "LeadWorks",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "lead-works.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "josh@studiokasa.art",
    "name": "Josh kasper",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check-in Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T14:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Lost ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "aiden@aileadistix.com",
    "name": "Aiden Meeker",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T13:45:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "EYRA Vision",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "EYRA.VISION",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "dispatch@anafreight.org",
    "name": "Shandra Mebane",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-28T12:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "To generate leads",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Freight Brokering",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Small business shippers that ships within my niche",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gmail-GMass ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Several of years",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 252-375-1348",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "ecohen@cclending.net",
    "name": "Eric Cohen",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "CC Lending",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "cclending.net",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "patrick@secondsuntech.com",
    "name": "Patrick Bolchoz",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Bourhan:  this was the earliest available time.  Any shot we can meet sooner?  I'd like to get my double credits via my attendance at the list build conference call going.  Thanks!  PB",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Holistic Health & Wellness Tech / application / platform.",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "CPO, CHRO, Benefits Director, EAP Director,etc.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HighLevel CRM",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Not Defined.",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 352-262-3398",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "gio@g6platform.com",
    "name": "Giovanny Victome",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Followup on the kickoff call. We need to buy domains. ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "hlux2008@gmail.com",
    "name": "Harry Lux",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check-in Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T17:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Checking campaign progress and strategy moving forward ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "manager@newlinkagency.com",
    "name": "Nathan Higham ",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "william@crownplacements.com",
    "name": "William Nicholls",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Scale our sales placement agency.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We sell sales placement on the front end (sourcing & placing remote salsa reps) and management on the back end.",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Founders of coaching programs or running agencies who are in a growth period, generating at least $200k+ a month. Founder/CEO/Head of Sales. At this level, they are usually very ready to bring on reps fast, are easy going, move quickly and onboard asap.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We\u2019re setting up with Instantly, but open to suggestions as we\u2019re just starting.",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "$10,000-$25k+",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 864-997-5775",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "chris@advantoraconsulting.com",
    "name": "Krzysztof Wozniczek",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-27T12:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "I want get my first clients via cold emails",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Fractional IT delivery director services - consulting",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to target CEOs or other titles in IT comapnies - IT companies that deliver IT maintenance and support services to other companies or plan to do it. MY target are companies which either have problems with setting up the IT support departments or struggle with their existing ones and need help",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "smartlead",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+48 788 309 882",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "bdove@vertuagent.com",
    "name": "Ben Dove",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Vertu Agent",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "vertuagent.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "chad@graphicfx.com",
    "name": "Chad McKay",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T18:15:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Graphic FX",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "graphicfx.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "andrew.bissada@gmail.com",
    "name": "Andrew Bissada",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "karnrsc4@gmail.com",
    "name": "Karn Chauhan",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "sell my automations ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "autonomy ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We only sell to B2B service companies that already generate leads and have sales teams, but are leaking revenue because their follow-up, routing, and ops are manual.Outbound agencies, marketing agencies, appointment setting firms, recruiting firms, and high-ticket B2B services.\n",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "emailbison",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "10,001 - 15,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "alot ",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+91 98187 77880",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rod@spadafy.com",
    "name": "Rod Janson",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Spadafy",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.spadafy.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jerry@817biz.com",
    "name": "Jerry Scott",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Subscriber acquisiton",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Local business news about our regional market",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "People who are interested in news and in particular business news.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Beehiiv",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 817-475-2658",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "timh@parcelink.com",
    "name": "Timothy Michael Hennip",
    "event_name": "Check-in",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T16:20:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "go over new campaigns",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rjeffs@callegra.com",
    "name": "Rich Jeffs",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "to get better results with cold emails",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Robocall blocker for hospitals and elderly care facilities",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Any Hospital or care facility CMO, CIO CISO, CNO, IT Director, IT Manager Hospital administrator, Director ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "company email but would like to send from Hubspot",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 801-988-6811",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "micah@freightfirstlogistics.com",
    "name": "Micah Huxford",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-26T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "giannic@10xworkforce.com",
    "name": "Gianni Cotteta",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "book more calls",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "recruiting",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "hvac, plumber, pipe fitters, ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "constant contact",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "100000",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 646-515-1002",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "alpha1contactme@gmail.com",
    "name": "Albert Saggese",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Albert Saggese",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "https://theemployeewellnessplan.com/",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "completecarecleaningsc@gmail.com",
    "name": "Darin Jackson",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Double my monthly revenue ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I help commercial properties with Cleaning needs",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "My perfect customer is Commercial offices. Any company with a office building that has a warehouse. My contact is the office manager or the facility manager or the operations manager. ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Completecarecleaningsc@gmail.com",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "8-10 years",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 803-818-2993",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "m.tepper@tpsprepaid.com",
    "name": "Mark Tepper",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "mjohnson@pvmic.com",
    "name": "Matt Johnson",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T17:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Build prospect list and review email copy",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "nvlvlv@gmail.com",
    "name": "Salim Ali",
    "event_name": "Listkit Fran\u00e7ois 1on1 Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T16:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "I want ti build a cold calling and email List.  I do Group insurance and commercial lending..  \n",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "david@sgracefacilities.com",
    "name": "David Petcove",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Sgrace facilities",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Sgracefacilities.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "bolen@formvue.com",
    "name": "Robert Bolen",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call ",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Kickoff Call ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jessica@rescuingleftovercuisine.org",
    "name": "Jessica NG",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Mo had a family emergency so I'll meet you",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "justin@proactivemktg.com",
    "name": "Justin Chua",
    "event_name": "Launch Review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T14:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "javiersanchez@masterfireprevention.com",
    "name": "Javier Sanchez",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-23T14:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Review Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "victor@vespermedia.net",
    "name": "Victor IP",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T20:15:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "joe@hyper-scale.co.uk",
    "name": "Joe Stevens",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Hyper Scale",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "hyper-scale.co.uk",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "amandeep@memorilabs.ai",
    "name": "Amandeep Sandhu",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check-in Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Check-in on campaign performance and strategy",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "a.munoz@binhex.cloud",
    "name": "Alba Mu\u00f1oz",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T19:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "We aim to generate high-quality leads and increase engagement with prospects.\nOur goal is to identify and convert interested companies efficiently.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We provide Binhex Cloud, an open-source ERP solution.\nIt helps SMEs streamline operations, finance, and sales processes.",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Our ideal customer is a growing SME with 10\u2013200 employees.\nWe typically contact decision-makers like CFOs, Operations, or IT Managers who value efficiency and flexibility.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We send emails through our corporate domain using a verified email server. All campaigns are personalized and tracked for engagement metrics.",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 786-820-3958",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "mkelley@healthwaresystems.com",
    "name": "Mike Kelley",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T17:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "New Campaign",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "laurie@ribus.com",
    "name": "Laurie Van Gels",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T16:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "RIBUS, Inc.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.ribus.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "greatrailing@hotmail.com",
    "name": "Chris Sibbert",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "great railing",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.greatrailing.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "mfps2@aol.com",
    "name": "Peter Martinez",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Setup Launch review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T14:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "childers.ben@gmail.com",
    "name": "Ben Childers",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T14:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Reformed Design LLC",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "www.reformedco.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "founder@ailelevate.com",
    "name": "Chintamani Modak",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-22T13:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Getting GTM support for my lead gebartion process bassd on  my  B2B saas profuct RetainIQ by aielevate pte.ltd. Singapore ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "SaaS",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "B2B SaaS subscription based cpmpanoes SMB and enterprise ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gmail",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+65 9170 7508",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "bishop@truerankdigital.com",
    "name": "Matt Bishop",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "We already had a meeting, this is a second follow up. ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Digital marketing. ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We have several ICP's",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "SendGrid, several platforms. ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "12 months",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 417-629-7373",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "brandi@chartec.net",
    "name": "Brandi Rogers",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Depends on the product",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "marketing agency that caters to IT Companies",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Each one of my clients caters to different types of businesses. My ideal client is an IT Company also known as an MSP that is between the 10-50 employee range. ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Glasshive and Hubspot",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 619-808-8059",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "juan@machfunding.com",
    "name": "Juan Paz",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "mach funding",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MAchfunding.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "christopher16365@yahoo.com",
    "name": "Chris Fontaine",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "initiate leads through cold email campaign (Biz is new)",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Sell targeted leads to higher-ticket clients",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M&A firms, Finance Firms",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None yet",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "15,000+ leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Not sure",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 301-538-2582",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "brianscottporter@gmail.com",
    "name": "Brian Porter",
    "event_name": "Check-in",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T16:20:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "buying domains ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tony@machfunding.com",
    "name": "TONY BODE",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Zeina Antonios",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "MACH FUNDING",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WWW.MACHFUNDING.COM",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tana@blueriveragency.com",
    "name": "Tana Bui",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T15:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "reach business owners",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "lead gen for recruitment agencies",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Recruitment agencies owners who's looking to have a reliable client acquisition so that they no longer have to rely on referrals.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Smartleads",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+44 7476 697053",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "bill@idatlanta.com",
    "name": "Bill Frey",
    "event_name": "Launch Review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-21T15:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "I have a tight calendar here and have another call at 11 so have to keep it 30 minutes or under ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "larrydlafferty@securityworldllc.com",
    "name": "Larry Lafferty",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "16 site surveys per month",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "security systems",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A higher end business owner, CEO or manager looking for security for their home or business",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "My email contacts",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "20 years",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 719-517-9090",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "chrissibbert@yahoo.com",
    "name": "Chris Sibbert",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T19:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "great railing",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "greatrailing.com",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "steve@ottosync.ai",
    "name": "Steve Ottman",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "To increase number of discovery calls booked.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We sell lead capture texting services for small businesses, as well as sms-based reactivation campaigns.",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A small service business who has trouble taking calls while they are busy throughout the day, and doesn't want to hire a receptionist. Or a small business with a list of past clients contact information who doesn't run reactivation campaigns.",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have a set of email addresses attached to various domains",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 207-286-5629",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jacqueline@forgeadvisors.io",
    "name": "Jacqueline Catala",
    "event_name": "Launch Review Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Emails are incorrect",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rajka@bigboost.com",
    "name": "Rajini Kanth",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "BigBoost AI",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "http://bigboost.agency/",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jledoux@qboai.com",
    "name": "Jimmy Ledoux",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Catch up.  Sorry I missed Friday.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "rohan@rhocash.com",
    "name": "Rohan Mishra",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-20T12:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Fran\u00e7ois Bonja",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Build my GTM engine to reach about 10k prospects a month and achieve 0.8% conversion",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "AP automation and agentic platform",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Probably manufacturing, logistics, d2c, ecommerce and any industry that has high invoice volume, distributed vendor base but a small team of finance",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Instantly",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+91 95353 86632",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "llee3@plananalysts.com",
    "name": "Laurence Lee",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "out bound email contacting leading to phone calls to set in person appointments",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Employee Benefits (Health insurance) plans and health management for EMPLOYERS",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "50 to 250 employees covered - any industry - near northeast florida",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "constant contact",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "depends",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 904-476-0614",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tram.holloway@gmail.com",
    "name": "Tram Holloway",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T19:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "retargerting outreach ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "robericksanders@gmail.com",
    "name": "Roberick Sanders",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T19:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "mariastockaca@gmail.com",
    "name": "Maria",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T19:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Rescheduled meeting for Jeff",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "sarkodiestefan@gmail.com",
    "name": "Stefan Sarkodie",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "As a real estate wholesaler , I'm just looking for different opportunties to market. ",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "We are essentially brokers for peoiples homes and linking them to a buyer. ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Someone who is willing to sell their home and trust me in finding a buyer. ",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Not doing any emails at the moment ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+44 7305 468091",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "tcates@brookeside.com",
    "name": "Thomas Cates",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T18:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Suggestions on changes to program",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "bryan.lopez@olympolabs.com",
    "name": "Bryan Lopez ",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "yonasyg123@gmail.com",
    "name": "yonas yihun",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check-in Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T18:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Daniel Hmedeh",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "campaign",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "emma@ugccreatorcollective.com",
    "name": "Emma Lorrae",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T17:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Ugc clients",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Ugc ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "tech/apps/saas/dtc",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "emma.lorrae@ugccreatorcollective.com",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5,001 - 10,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 832-335-8408",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "yisrael@costcuttingconsultant.com",
    "name": "yisrael markowitz",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Kickoff Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T17:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "ccc",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Company Name"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ccc",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "Website URL"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I will show up to the call on time using a laptop or desktop computer",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Do you agree to show up to the call ON TIME and using a laptop or desktop computer?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes, I have signed and am ready to start onboarding! ",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Please make sure to sign the agreement so we can smoothly kick off our partnership."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "ecm.paperless@gmail.com",
    "name": "David James",
    "event_name": "Check-in",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T16:20:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Mo Shemy",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Updates on system. Where are we at? Where are we going? Share the plan of action.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "seanb@vertexprivatefunding.com",
    "name": "Sean Bristol",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Lead Generation Strategy Call \ud83d\ude80",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T16:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "150 loans a year",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Commercial Mortgage Broker",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Investors and Real Estate Brokers and Agents",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HighConversion",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "30000",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am an active ListKit user",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "This call is only available to active ListKit users. If you are not an active ListKit user, we will cancel the call."
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 347-210-1199",
        "position": 7,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "ivan@inspacelabs.com",
    "name": "Ivan Malenica",
    "event_name": "ListKit DFY Cold Email Setup Launch Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-19T15:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Hael Al Assaad",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Launch Call",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "Please share anything that will help prepare for our meeting."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "jim.consumerloans@gmail.com",
    "name": "Jim Loser",
    "event_name": "1-on-1 Listkit Demo & Data Strategy Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-16T20:00:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Majd Azzam",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Increase financing client contact for business to consumer decision makers with Home Improvement Retail Contractors.",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What are your growth goals with using ListKit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "financing business to consumer for Home Improvement Retail Contractors, Coaching/Seminar, Elective Medical and Retail Industries. ",
        "position": 1,
        "question": "What does your company sell and who does it help?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HVAC, Roofing business owner or president/cfo",
        "position": 2,
        "question": "Who's your perfect customer? Think about your favorite customer - what type of company are they, what role does your contact have there, and what made them such a great fit?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Email Jim.consumerloans@gmail.com",
        "position": 3,
        "question": "Where are you currently sending emails from?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "1,000 - 5,000 leads per month",
        "position": 4,
        "question": "How many leads do you want to send cold emails to per month?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "5 years of financing at $60k per year or $300k over 5 years",
        "position": 5,
        "question": "What is the lifetime value (LTV) of your clients?"
      },
      {
        "answer": "+1 760-458-7621",
        "position": 6,
        "question": "What is your phone number? "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "email": "gunther@dominateorganicsearch.com",
    "name": "Gunther Mueller",
    "event_name": "ListKit's DFY Cold Email Check In Call",
    "event_date": "2026-01-16T19:30:00.000000Z",
    "host": "Yasir Ghufran",
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "answer": "Getting Our Campaign Going",
        "position": 0,
        "question": "What is this call about?"
      }
    ]
  }
]